You promised me that you [music] would
never ever leave me crying.
never ever let me go. But suddenly
something went wrong. I should have
known it all. Heat. Heat. Heat.
[music]
Time to say goodbye.
We can't be through now.
We never really got a [music] chance to
start.
Maybe it's just too soon to say [music]
goodbye.
What can I do now to keep you in [music]
my arms and keep the passion in your
heart?
Baby, it's [music] just too soon to say
goodbye.
We can be through now. Give it some
time. We never really got a chance to
start.
Maybe it's just too soon to [music] say
goodbye.
What can I do now to keep you in [music]
my arms and keep the passion in your
heart?
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat.